[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name brontosaurus is derived from the Greek words sauros, which means lizard, combined with another word. What does the word bronte mean?", "correct_answer": "Thunder or roar", "incorrect_answers": ["Large", "Long neck", "Poetic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You should dilute this amount of essential oil into 100ml (3.25 fl oz.) of base oil.", "correct_answer": "20 - 60 drops", "incorrect_answers": ["100 - 150 drops", "50 - 70 drops", "30 - 80 drops"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie \u201cTo Sir, with Love\u201d stars Sidney Poitier as a teacher confronted with a class of arrogant and provocative students. In what city is the movie set?", "correct_answer": "London", "incorrect_answers": ["Liverpool", "San Francisco", "New York City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the team in Hoosiers call the play where two players line up shoulder to shoulder, setting a big pick for the shooter?", "correct_answer": "Picket fence", "incorrect_answers": ["Picket wall", "Super pickpick", "Double pick em"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Bigfoot Lore, who was Albert Ostman?", "correct_answer": "A man who claimed to be kidnapped by a Bigfoot", "incorrect_answers": ["The first scientist to declare Bigfoot a hoax", "Owner of the Bigfoot restaurant in Portland, Oregon", "The first man to see Bigfoot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This United States Navy aircraft was used widely during the Second World War.", "correct_answer": "F4U Corsair", "incorrect_answers": ["B17 Flying Fortress", "F-5 Tiger", "P47 Thunderbolt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A single shot (1 ounce) of espresso contains more caffeine than a 7-ounce cup of drip coffee.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most amount of wolf pups ever recorded in a litter?", "correct_answer": "14 pups", "incorrect_answers": ["4 pups", "5 pups", "10 pups"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first US President to publish a mathematical proof?", "correct_answer": "James Garfield", "incorrect_answers": ["Benjamin Pierce", "Thomas Jefferson", "Herbert Hoover"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Tomato Frogs are in captivity at a zoo, what kind of food are they fed?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin-dusted crickets and mealworms.", "incorrect_answers": ["Grass, seaweed, and other vegetation", "Small fish, such as minnows and guppies", "The same food they would eat in the wild"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do platypuses reproduce?", "correct_answer": "Platypuses lay eggs.", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Platypuses reproduce asexually.", "Platypuses are metatherian."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the way Michelangelo drew the snake in the Sistine Chapel?", "correct_answer": "The snake is a woman", "incorrect_answers": ["The snake is walking", "The snake appears to be speaking", "The snake has no fangs"]}]